http://www.thedigeratilife.com/privacy-policy-for-the-digerati-life/

Privacy Policy For The Digerati Life
We take the privacy of our visitors to The Digerati Life very seriously.
At The Digerati Life, we recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit The Digerati Life, and how we safeguard your information.
We never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.
The information in the log files includes your IP (internet protocol) address, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We do use cookies to store information, such as the user name you left a comment under, when you visit our site.
We also use third party advertisements on The Digerati Life to support our site.
Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.
This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.
However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.
For more information, check here.
Copyright © 2006-2017 June Tree. All Rights Reserved.
Disclaimer, Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
